<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Aural Skills III]]></title>
  <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-24T10:50:18-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Kris Shaffer]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[kris.shaffer@colorado.edu]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[U2: New Years Day video]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/u2-new-years-day-video/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-24T10:48:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/u2-new-years-day-video</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As requested, and just for fun.</p>

<p>First, the one shown in class:</p>

<iframe width="420" height="315" src="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3//www.youtube.com/embed/PPVi0f8lKSc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p>And then my favorite:</p>

<iframe width="420" height="315" src="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3//www.youtube.com/embed/RsVJfT-L_dA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prep for Oct. 23/24 and 28/29 (UPDATE)]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/prep-for-oct-23-slash-24-and-28-slash-29/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-18T11:14:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/prep-for-oct-23-slash-24-and-28-slash-29</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>All students:</h2>

<p>By you Oct. 28/29 class meeting, work with your group to transcribe at least the first <em>cycle</em> of your song (first strophe in a strophic song, first verse–(prechorus)–chorus in a V-C song). Put your transcription in music notation software.</p>

<p>Make a folder in Google Drive with all group members&#8217; last names and &#8220;Unit 2 transcription&#8221; in the folder title. Share it with all group members and your instructor, with editing privileges. Make a PDF of your transcription, and upload it to that folder.</p>

<h2>Shaffer section:</h2>

<p>For Wednesday, Oct. 23, listen to <a href="http://open.spotify.com/track/7IzLAli1EfsUYTLgfp4MvM">New Years Day</a> (spotify URI: spotify:track:7IzLAli1EfsUYTLgfp4MvM). Follow along with the keyboard part on the score in the MUSC 2121 shared materials folder in GDrive.</p>

<iframe src="https://embed.spotify.com/?uri=spotify:track:7IzLAli1EfsUYTLgfp4MvM" width="300" height="380" frameborder="0" allowtransparency="true"></iframe>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prep for Oct. 21]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/prep-for-oct-21/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-15T10:50:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/prep-for-oct-21</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Listen to Radiohead&#8217;s <a href="http://open.spotify.com/track/1lv2cq78vX9q9Sz8uqkTSu">&#8220;Packt Like Sardines in a Crushd Tin Box&#8221;</a> (Spotify URI: spotify:track:1lv2cq78vX9q9Sz8uqkTSu) while following along with the <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/media/PacktTimeline.pdf">timeline</a> I created. Listen several times until you can identify each of the elements by ear while listening. If you have difficulty with a specific element or passage, post a question on Piazza.</p>

<p>Also, find a partner or partners for the transcription project and choose a song. If more than one group select the same song, we&#8217;ll negotiate that on Monday. Come with a second choice, just in case.</p>

<p>Bring staff and notebook paper to class on Monday.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prep for Oct. 16/17]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/prep-for-oct-16/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-10T14:54:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/prep-for-oct-16</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Before class on Wednesday/Thursday, Oct. 16/17, update your self-evaluation to reflect your sight-singing exam, and read the Unit III Guide. Come to class with any questions you have about the guide.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unit II portfolio]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/unit-ii-portfolio/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-08T08:14:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/unit-ii-portfolio</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unit II materials are due before class on Monday/Tuesday, Oct. 14/15. Your Unit II portfolio should include the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>a video of a (nearly) flawless performance of &#8220;Der Neugierige&#8221; uploaded to Google Drive; clearly lableled with your last name, the song title, and &#8220;FINAL&#8221; in the file name; and shared with your instructor.</li>
<li>a video of a (nearly) flawless performance of &#8220;Der Müller und der Bach&#8221; uploaded to Google Drive; clearly lableled with your last name, the song title, and &#8220;FINAL&#8221; in the file name; and shared with your instructor.</li>
<li>one example of each of the six rhythmic categories on the Unit II Guide, posted on Piazza under the appropriate heading, and vetted by your classmates.</li>
<li>An updated self-evaluation containing grades and comments for <em>standard rhythms</em>, <em>irregular division of the beat</em>, <em>diatonicism in tonal melodies</em>, <em>chromaticism in tonal melodies</em>, <em>modulation to closely related keys</em>, <em>performance</em>, <em>transcription (aural recognition)</em>, and <em>professionalism</em>. Your grades and comments should reference all relevant work this semester, not only Unit II.</li>
</ul>


<p>If you have any questions or difficulties, contact your instructor well ahead of the deadline.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 12 supplemental assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/meeting-12-supplemental-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-04T13:17:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/meeting-12-supplemental-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>FOR SHAFFER SECTION ONLY:</p>

<p>In addition to <a href="http://cutheory.github.io/auralskills3/2013/10/meeting-11-and-12-assignment/">the assignment already posted</a> for Tuesday morning, also take the <a href="http://learningcatalytics.com">Learning Catalytics</a> quiz on the cadences in &#8220;Erlkönig&#8221; (session ID 731080) before Wednesday&#8217;s class. Some of these were already covered in class. You can find the video played in class <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C3nxyS8wf8E">here</a>. Audio recordings abound. The score passed out in class can be downloaded <a href="http://javanese.imslp.info/files/imglnks/usimg/7/7c/IMSLP15041-SchubertD328_Erlk__nig_4th_version.pdf">here</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 11 &amp; 12 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/meeting-11-and-12-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-01T12:58:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/10/meeting-11-and-12-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For <em>the day after meeting 12 (Tues./Wed., Oct. 8/9)</em>, do the following:</p>

<ul>
<li>Respond to at least six of your classmates&#8217; rhythm excerpts on Piazza, as before. Affirm or critique (gently and helpfully).</li>
<li>Make a video of yourself singing &#8220;Der Müller und der Bach&#8221; as accurately as possible, noting modulations in your syllables, and submit it to your instructor via Google Drive.</li>
</ul>


<p>This will take quite some time, so be sure not to wait until Monday/Tuesday evening to begin. And do use a recording, a keyboard, or a classmate as you learn &#8220;Der Müller und der Bach,&#8221; so that you can get those modulations and chromatic-chord arpeggios into your ear.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 10 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-10-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-27T15:13:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-10-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For Meeting 11 (Oct. 2/3), fill out your Unit II rhythmic portfolio on Piazza. For each of the six categories, make sure you have provided one correct example in Piazza. If excerpts you previously have submitted have been confirmed by your colleagues or instructor, don&#8217;t worry about that category. However, for categories you have not attempted yet, or for categories where your example was proven incorrect by your colleagues or instructor, provide a new example.</p>

<p><strong>Make sure you are clear on compound meter. 5/4, 7/4, etc. are <em>not</em> compound meter.</strong> Also, please help your classmates and instructor out by using Spotify, rather than YouTube, if possible. Those YouTube commercials are getting longer and popping up more frequently.</p>

<p>If, for whatever reason (I know a few of you were sick), you did not get the video of &#8220;Der Neugierige&#8221; in on Friday, get that in ASAP.</p>

<p>Also, begin practicing &#8220;Der Müller und der Bach.&#8221; A video attempt of that song will be due later this week.</p>

<p>Finally, note that we will be extending the singing part of Unit II beyond the initial target of Oct. 2/3. More details will come soon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 9 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-9-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-24T19:35:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-9-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For 8am on Friday, Sept. 27, make a video of your performance of the entire movement of &#8220;Der Neugierige&#8221; (movement VI of <em>Die schöne Müllerin</em>: <a href="https://play.spotify.com/user/kris.shaffer/playlist/1SaXv4tlZlW931nZ9a8q1o">recording</a>, <a href="http://imslp.org/wiki/Special:ImagefromIndex/03233">score</a>) upload to Google Drive, and share with your instructor.</p>

<p>If you have any questions about the modulations or syllables beyond what is discussed in class, use Piazza to consult with each other and/or your instructor.</p>

<p>For Meeting 10 (Mon./Tues., Sept. 30/Oct. 1), print out the score to &#8220;Der Müller und der Bach,&#8221; listen to it (same playlist and score as above), and mark all cadences by key and cadence type.</p>

<p>Also, practice the harmonic sequentials and arpeggio exercises distributed in class.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 8 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-8-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-19T09:59:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-8-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For 8am the day after Meeting 8 (Tuesday/Wednesday, Sept. 24/25), make a video of your performance of p. 1 of &#8220;Der Neugierige&#8221; (movement VI of <em>Die schöne Müllerin</em>: <a href="https://play.spotify.com/user/kris.shaffer/playlist/1SaXv4tlZlW931nZ9a8q1o">recording</a>, <a href="http://imslp.org/wiki/Special:ImagefromIndex/03233">score</a>) upload to Google Drive, and share with your instructor.</p>

<p>For Meeting 9 (Wednesday/Thursday, Sept. 25/26), listen to &#8220;Der Neugierige&#8221;, and for every harmonic cadence, note the key and cadence type (PAC/IAC/HC) on the score and bring to class.</p>

<p>Also, practice the harmonic sequentials and arpeggio exercises distributed in class.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 7 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-7-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-17T13:16:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-7-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>By 8am the day after meeting 7 (Sept. 19), SHAFFER&#8217;s section only:</em></p>

<p>Log in to <a href="http://learningcatalytics.com">Learning Catalytics</a> (purchase a semester license if you have not already), and enter session ID 56392 to take a quiz on &#8220;Die böse Farbe&#8221; from <em>Die schöne Müllerin</em>. Have your score handy, and answer the questions about keys in the song. You may also use a recording (such as Ian Bostridge, <a href="spotify:user:kris.shaffer:playlist:1SaXv4tlZlW931nZ9a8q1o">available on Spotify</a>) or a keyboard.</p>

<p><em>Before meeting 8 (Sept. 23/24), ALL STUDENTS:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Respond to at least 6 examples listed by your classmates in the collaborative playlists on Piazza. If their example is correct, say so. If not, offer a respectful correction, adding the example to another playlist if necessary.</li>
<li>Begin practicing your first prepared song (&#8220;Die Neugerige&#8221;, from <em>Die schöne Müllerin</em>). A video atempt <em>of page 1</em> will be due the day after Meeting 8 (Sept. 25/26), so make use of the weekend to prepare well.</li>
</ul>


<p>Be sure to bring your copy of <em>Die schöne Müllerin</em> to class, as well as any other materials your instructor has required (none for Shaffer).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 6 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-6-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-16T12:53:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-6-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>Before Meeting 7 (Sept. 18/19), please do the following:</em></p>

<ul>
<li>Finish updating your self-evaluation for the end of Unit I, if necessary.</li>
<li>Read the resource on <a href="http://kris.shaffermusic.com/musicianship/chromaticSolfege.html">chromatic solfège</a> and come prepared to sing the sequentials in that resource in class.</li>
<li>Bring a printed or digital copy of <a href="http://imslp.org/wiki/Special:ImagefromIndex/03233"><em>Die schöne Müllerin</em></a> to class.</li>
<li>Find at least three examples (total, <em>not</em> three of each kind!) of the rhythmic features listed in the Unit II guide. List them in Piazza under the appropriate post. <em>Do not repeat examples provided by others in the class, including those in other sections.</em> This will be one large collection generated by all five sections of the course working together.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 5 assignmnment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-5-assignmnment/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-10T11:38:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-5-assignmnment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>By 8am the morning <strong>AFTER</strong> sight-singing exams (Sept. 12 for MW sections, Sept. 13 for TR sections):</em></p>

<p>Update your self-evaluation to include assessment of your complete Unit I video portfolio, and yoursight-singing exam. <strong><em>Give yourself a letter grade (without +/–) for each category covered by Unit I</em></strong> according to the guide at the end of the &#8220;Assessment&#8221; page on this site, and support that letter grade with evidence from your class activities in Unit I.</p>

<p><em>Before Meeting 6 (Sept. 16/17):</em></p>

<p>Read the <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/units/unit2.html">Unit II Guide</a>. Post any questions you have about the guide to Piazza for discussion there and/or in-class. Only questions posted on Piazza will be discussed in class. Please post them ahead of time.</p>

<p>Bring your Berkowitz anthology to class throughout Unit II, as well as a printout or digital version of <em>Die schöne Müllerin</em>, linked from the Unit II guide.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unit I portfolios]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/unit-i-portfolios/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-06T10:34:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/unit-i-portfolios</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Meeting 5 (Sept. 11/12) is the end of Unit I. Be sure to sign up for a rhythmic sight-singing exam slot for that day with your instructor.</p>

<p>Video portfolios must be completed, revised (if necessary), and shared with your instructor on Google Drive by 8am the morning of your Meeting 5 class day. Since this is the fourth round of video submissions, there has been plenty of time to work out any technological kinks, and therefore, there will be no late submissions accepted. Make sure that all seven exercises are included, and that they are as close to flawless as possible.</p>

<p>Please review the section on &#8220;summative assessments&#8221; on the <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/coursework">Coursework</a> page before submitting your portfolios and coming to your sight-singing exams.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 3 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-3-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-03T19:59:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/meeting-3-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>This assignment is due at 8am the morning <strong>AFTER</strong> Meeting 3 (Sept. 5 for MW sections, Sept. 6 for TR sections).</em></p>

<p>Record video of <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/units/2121-unit1-rhythms.pdf">portfolio exercises 6–7</a> with a partner and submit to instructor via Google Drive.</p>

<p>Be sure to have the Kazez text with you for every class meeting during Unit I.</p>

<h3>Additional notes</h3>

<p>If your videos of exercises 1–5 were not up to standard, budget time to redo those exercises soon. All seven videos will be due by Meeting 5 (Sept. 11/12).</p>

<p>A 1-minute video domonstrating uploading and sharing files on Google Drive can be found <a href="http://kris.shaffermusic.com/musicianship/GDrive.html">here</a>.</p>

<p>As usual, make use of Piazza if you have any questions about the course, the syllabus, the policies, the homework, or the technology.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on videos 5–7]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/video-5-7-notes/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-03T19:16:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/09/video-5-7-notes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Following are some general notes on the rhythm video submissions so far <em>for Kris Shaffer&#8217;s section (Section 3, MW 10am) only</em>. If you would like specific comments, please make an appointment to see me outside of class or drop by during office hours. Keep in mind that this is, in part, an exercise in self-evaluation. Before you come to me, make sure you have listened carefully to your video and identified/fixed any errors you find before coming to me for assistance. I will help you get over those final hurdles, but I want you to do as much yourself as possible.</p>

<p>First, a number of you are still having difficulty placing fast notes on the back side of the beat. (I.e., the final sixteenth note in a dotted-eighth and sixteenth rhythm.)</p>

<p>Second, make sure all long notes are sustained full value. This will help your accuracy when performing 2 or 4 against 3, among other things. Also, make sure that single-beat notes are always full value. This is easy to miss when the eighth note is the notated beat.</p>

<p>Third, <em>everyone</em> missed the tempo/beat instructions in number 3. It may have been stated unclearly, but the quarter-note beat in 3/4 and the dotted-quarter beat in 6/8 should be the same duration. As a result, the eighths and sixteenths should all get faster when it changes to 6/8 and slower when it changes to 3/4.</p>

<p>Last, make sure both performers are equally close to the computer/phone. In some of the videos, it is hard to hear one voice because it is drowned out by the other.</p>

<p>Please revisit all of your videos this week or this weekend in advance of next week&#8217;s submission. Tap a steady beat, division, or subdivision along with your performance, and look especially for the above errors. If you do so, you will find most of the mistakes and imprecisions that are present. Do everything thing you can to submit videos that are as <em>perfect</em> as you can make them.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 2 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/meeting-2-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-27T15:17:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/meeting-2-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>This assignment is due at 8am the morning <strong>before</strong> Meeting 3 (Sept. 3 for MW sections, Sept. 4 for TR sections).</em></p>

<p>Record video of <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/units/2121-unit1-rhythms.pdf">portfolio exercises 3–5</a> with a partner and submit to instructor via Google Drive.</p>

<p>Also, please begin work on your self-evaluation. Comment on your progress on all concepts/skills addressed in class so far (standard rhythms, irregular division of the beat, performance, professionalism).</p>

<p>Be sure to have the Kazez text with you for every class meeting during Unit I.</p>

<h3>Additional notes</h3>

<p>If your videos of exercises 1–2 were not up to standard (or if you had tech/partner/course schedule issues that prevented you from completing them on time), the long weekend is a great opportunity to (re)do those exercises. All seven videos will be due by Meeting 5 (Sept. 11/12).</p>

<p>A 1-minute video domonstrating uploading and sharing files on Google Drive can be found <a href="http://kris.shaffermusic.com/musicianship/GDrive.html">here</a>.</p>

<p>As usual, make use of Piazza if you have any questions about the course, the syllabus, the policies, the homework, or the technology.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting 1 assignment]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/meeting-1-assignment/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-23T15:10:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/meeting-1-assignment</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>This assignment is due at 8am the morning after Meeting 1 (Aug 27. for MW sections, Aug. 28 for TR sections).</em></p>

<p>Record video of <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/units/2121-unit1-rhythms.pdf">portfolio exercises 1 &amp; 2</a> with a partner and submit to instructor via Google Drive.</p>

<p>Section 3 (Kris Shaffer) students, also make a 1–2 minute video introducing yourself: Who are you? Where are you from? What are your goals? (in life, and in this class) This will help me get to know you better.</p>

<p>A 1-minute video domonstrating uploading and sharing files on Google Drive can be found <a href="http://kris.shaffermusic.com/musicianship/GDrive.html">here</a>.</p>

<p>All students, please make use of Piazza if you have any questions about the course, the syllabus, the policies, the homework, or the technology. It is a great tool for building community outside of class, even between the five sections of this course.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Meeting 1 (Aug. 26/27)]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/for-monday/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-22T11:06:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/for-monday</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome (back) to Boulder!</p>

<p>Before our first meeting, please read the <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/syllabus/">syllabus</a>, <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/assessment/">assessment</a>, <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/coursework/">coursework</a>, and <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/policies/">policies</a> pages for this course, as well as the <a href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/units/unit1.html">Unit I guide</a>. Note any questions you have about these documents.</p>

<p>Also, please bring a web-enabled device to class—such as a smartphone, tablet, or laptop—and your copy of Kazez, <em>Rhythm Reading</em>.</p>

<p>I (Kris Shaffer) and the TAs look forward to meeting all of you soon!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Piazza]]></title>
    <link href="http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/piazza/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-22T10:22:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://CUTheory.github.com/auralskills3/2013/08/piazza</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This term we will be using Piazza for class discussion. The system is highly catered to getting you help fast and efficiently from classmates and myself. Rather than emailing questions about course materials directly to me, I encourage you to post your questions on Piazza. If you have any problems or feedback for the developers, email <a href="mailto:team@piazza.com">team@piazza.com</a>.</p>

<p>Of course, matters of a private nature should <em>not</em> be addressed on Piazza. Please email me about private concerns, or better yet, come by my office so we can discuss them in person.</p>

<p>Find our class Piazza page at: <a href="https://piazza.com/colorado/fall2013/musc2121/home">https://piazza.com/colorado/fall2013/musc2121/home</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
